<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Dave Pereira</title><link>https://davepereira.co.uk/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Dave Pereira</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davepereira.co.uk/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://davepereira.co.uk/page/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davepereira.co.uk/page/about/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="about-david-the-digital-marketing-enthusiast-and-slightly-obsessed-marathon-runner">About David: The Digital Marketing Enthusiast (and Slightly Obsessed Marathon Runner)&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Hey! Welcome to my blog. I&amp;rsquo;m David, and if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who gets genuinely excited about making things happen online, you&amp;rsquo;ve landed in the right place. For the past 8 years, I&amp;rsquo;ve been knee-deep in the wonderful world of digital marketing, with a particular knack for conquering the Amazon jungle and wrangling unruly email lists.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="my-love-affair-with-amazon-and-a-few-marketplace-wins">My Love Affair with Amazon (and a few marketplace wins)&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Let&amp;rsquo;s talk Amazon. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a giant online store to me; it&amp;rsquo;s a strategic battlefield, and frankly, I love a good campaign. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent years getting cozy with Amazon&amp;rsquo;s marketplace responsibilities, strategically optimizing and implementing PPC campaigns. You know those product listings that just make you want to click &amp;ldquo;Add to Cart&amp;rdquo;? Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m kind of obsessed with those. I dive deep into market analysis, A/B testing, claims validation, and customer insights to develop compelling product listings. I even helped launch new products on the marketplace, expanding portfolios like a digital explorer charting new lands. It&amp;rsquo;s all about making sure your products aren&amp;rsquo;t just on Amazon, but winning on Amazon.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>